Finding Aid for the Louis Thurston Nicholas Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- CORRESPONDENCE - INCOMING
  - Following Greyhound Bus Wreck, 1959 –Smith –Swor (Box 80, Folder 9))
  - Following Greyhound Bus Wreck, 1959 –Taylor – Tuley (Box 80, Folder 10))
  - Following Greyhound Bus Wreck, 1959 –Unsun – Vohes (Box 80, Folder 11))
  - Following Greyhound Bus Wreck, 1959 –Wade – Williamson (Box 80, Folder 12))
  - Following Greyhound Bus Wreck, 1959 –Wolfe –Zepernick (Box 80, Folder 13))
  - Condolences on Hospital Stay (1988) –Abney –Bubis (Box 81, Folder 1))
  - Condolences on Hospital Stay (1988) –Callaway – Croy (Box 81, Folder 2))
  - Condolences on Hospital Stay (1988)—Dawson – Graham (Box 81, Folder 3))
  - Condolences onHospital Stay (1988)—Hill – Johnson (Box 81, Folder 4))
  - Condolences on Hospital Stay (1988)—K – L (Box 81, Folder 5))
  - Condolences on Hospital Stay (1988) –M’s (Box 81, Folder 6))
  - Condolences on Hospital Stay (1988) – N- R (Box 81, Folder 7))
  - Condolences on Hospital Stay (1988) --S’s (Box 81, Folder 8))
  - Condolences on Hospital Stay (1988) --Tarpley – Z (Box 81, Folder 9))
  - Responses to Letters of Condolence, 1979, 1982, 1985- 1986, 1988 –1989, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 10))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 15, 1990—Abney – Borthick (Box 82, Folder 1))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Bradley – Copple (Box 82, Folder 2))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Cormier – Dye (Box 82, Folder 3))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Early – Foster (Box 82, Folder 4))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990—Forstman – Fusner (Box 82, Folder 5))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –George – Harrison (Box 82, Folder 6))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Hartgerlink – Holl (Box 82, Folder 7))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Hooe – Kelton (Box 82, Folder 8))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990—Lacey –McCroskey (Box 83, Folder 1))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –McWhirter – Noble (Box 83, Folder 2))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Olmstead – Presser (Box 83, Folder 3))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990—Read – Roberts (Box 83, Folder 4))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Sawyer – Small (Box 83, Folder 5))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Smedley – Snow (Box 83, Folder 6))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Spencer – Tuck (Box 83, Folder 7))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Vine Street Christian Church (Box 83, Folder 8))
  - Condolences on Sally’s death May 1990 –Wade –Zielinski (Box 83, Folder 9))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean—Arts Appreciation Foundation, Inc (Box 84, Folder 1))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean—Aspen Musical Festival –Bright, John (Box 84, Folder 2))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean—Cherry – Di Carlo (Box 84, Folder 3))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean—Festival de Musique Montreux (Box 84, Folder 4))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean—Festival de Musique Montreuz (Box 84, Folder 5))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean—Fitzpatrick – Hieronymous (Box 84, Folder 6))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean—Holland Festival – K (Box 84, Folder 7))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean---Litchford – Lufthansa (Box 84, Folder 8))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean—McKinley – Morris (Box 84, Folder 9))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean – Parrish – Ramber (Box 84, Folder 10))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean –Sound and Fury – Tregillus (Box 84, Folder 11))
  - Concerning affiliation to The Tennessean – Weinstein – Zalban (Box 84, Folder 12))
  - Publicity letters to The Tennessean—B-G (Box 84, Folder 13))
  - Publicity letters to The Tennessean—H-L (Box 84, Folder 14))
  - Publicity letters to The Tennessean – Music Critics Assoc. – National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences (Box 84, Folder 15))
  - Publicity letters to The Tennessean—M- P (Box 84, Folder 16))
  - Publicity letters to The Tennessean— R –S (Box 84, Folder 17))
  - Publicity letters to The Tennessean— T- W (Box 84, Folder 18))
  - The Tennessean— Abney – Bradley (Box 84, Folder 19))
  - The Tennessean – Breeden – Fossick (Box 84, Folder 20))
  - The Tennessean –Gaines – Hurt (Box 84, Folder 21))
  - The Tennessean –Jackson – Lyon (Box 84, Folder 22))
  - The Tennessean – McCracken – Myers (Box 84, Folder 23))
  - The Tennessean –Naff – Rossin (Box 84, Folder 24))
  - The Tennessean –Saint Bernard – Symmes (Box 84, Folder 25))
  - The Tennessean –Talley, Ruth – Zibart, Alan (Box 84, Folder 26))
  - The Tennessean—Letters of remonstrance, regrets, complaints, suggestions and letters to the Editor (Box 84, Folder 27))
  - The Tennessean—Responses to reviews (Box 84, Folder 28))
  - From College Presidents (Belmont – Trevecca Nazarene ) (Box 85, Folder 1))
  - From Colleagues at Peabody and Vanderbilt—Allen – Crabb (Box 85, Folder 2))
  - From Colleagues at Peabody and Vanderbilt—Crawford – Harrison (Mrs. Charles) (Box 85, Folder 3))
  - From Colleagues and Staff of Peabody College and Vanderbilt—Hazlehurst – McClurkan (Box 85, Folder 4))
  - From Colleagues and Staff of Peabody College and Vanderbilt—Miller – Rowley (Box 85, Folder 5))
  - From Colleagues and Staff of Peabody College and Vanderbilt—Shaver – Woodward (Box 85, Folder 6))
  - From Peabody College Presidents—John M. Claunch – John Dunworth (Box 85, Folder 7))
  - From Peabody College Presidents—Garrison, S.C. (Box 85, Folder 8))
  - From Peabody College Presidents –Eloise Hill – Henry Hill (Box 85, Folder 9))
  - From Peabody College Presidents—Payne – Felix Robb (Box 85, Folder 10))
  - From Prospective Peabody College Students –A –H (Box 85, Folder 11))
  - From Prospective Peabody College Students –H – K (Box 85, Folder 12))
  - From Prospective Peabody College Students- L – W (Box 85, Folder 13))
  - From Pupils (1) 1953, 1957- 1959, 1986 –1991, Anderson – Burt (Box 86, Folder 1))
  - From Pupils, Carrier – Darnell (Box 86, Folder 2))
  - From Pupils—David –Dodd (Box 86, Folder 3))
  - From Pupils—Fritz – Holdt (Box 86, Folder 4))
  - From Pupils –Hsu – Jennings (Box 86, Folder 5))
  - From Pupils—Johnson - Kauffman (Box 86, Folder 6))
  - From Pupils—Kelly – Lake (Box 86, Folder 7))
  - From Pupils—Mason – Phillips (Box 86, Folder 8))
  - From Pupils –Piche – Porter (Box 86, Folder 9))
  - From Pupils –R – Sapp (Box 86, Folder 10))
  - From Pupils –Sims – Thompson (Box 86, Folder 11))
  - From Pupils – Van Bramer – Wright (Box 86, Folder 12))
  - Inquiries about Study, etc.—Alderson – Franklin (Box 86, Folder 13))
  - Inquiries about Study, etc. –Frazier – Tucker (Box 86, Folder 14))
  - Inquiries about Study, etc. –Wade – Zawal (Box 86, Folder 15))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1956 – 1957 (Box 87, Folder 1))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 87, Folder 2))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 87, Folder 3))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 4))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 5))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 6))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 7))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 1))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 2))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1964 – 1965 (Box 88, Folder 3))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 4))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 5))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 88, Folder 6))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 7))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 8))
  - Peabody College, Summer Concert Series, Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 88, Folder 9))
  - Southwestern at Memphis—Faculty and Friends—Alexander – Bowden (Box 89, Folder 1))
  - Southwestern at Memphis—Faculty and Friends—Cloar – Guth (Box 89, Folder 2))
  - Southwestern at Memphis—Faculty and Friends –Heidelberg – Lineback (Box 89, Folder 3))
  - Southwestern at Memphis—Faculty and Friends –McIlwaine – Moss (Box 89, Folder 4))
  - Southwestern at Memphis –Faculty and Friends –Perry – Pond (Box 89, Folder 5))
  - Southwestern at Memphis –Faculty and Friends –Raines – Simmons (Box 89, Folder 6))
  - Southwestern at Memphis—Faculty and Friends—Smith, Winton – Weeks (Box 89, Folder 7))
  - Rhodes College (formerly Southwestern at Memphis) Daniel – Guth (Box 89, Folder 8))
  - Rhodes College—Faculty and Friends—Lineback – Ward (Box 89, Folder 9))
  - Southwestern at Memphis—Fund Raising Brochures (Box 89, Folder 10))
  - Southwestern News, Memphis, Tenn., January, 1941 – July 1945 (Box 89, Folder 11))
  - Alumni Association University of Michigan (Box 89, Folder 12))
- NATS (National Association of Teachers of Singing) CORRESPONDENCE AND OTHER MATERIALS
  - Correspondence and Memoranda, Reports (Box 90, Folder 1))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1954 (Box 90, Folder 2))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 90, Folder 3))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1956 (Box 90, Folder 4))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1957 – 1960 (Box 90, Folder 5))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1958 –1962 (Box 90, Folder 6))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, ca., 1960 – 1962 (Box 90, Folder 7))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1963 –1967 (Box 90, Folder 8))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1967 (Box 90, Folder 9))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1968 – 1969 (Box 90, Folder 10))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1969 – 1970 (Box 90, Folder 11))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1970 – 1972 (Box 90, Folder 12))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1972 –1975 (Box 90, Folder 13))
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 14))
  - Outgoing Correspondence—1962—Abee – Graves, Ruth (Box 91, Folder 1))
  - Outgoing Correspondence—1962 –Gunn, George W. – Lukken, Albert (Box 91, Folder 2))
  - Outgoing Correspondence—1962—McDonald, Florence –Selfridge, Cecil Blanche (Box 91, Folder 3))
  - Outgoing Correspondence—1962—Simpson – York, W. Wynn (Box 91, Folder 4))
  - Outgoing Correspondence –1963-1964—Gaietto – Wray (Box 91, Folder 5))
  - Outgoing Correspondence—1963-1964—A – C (Box 91, Folder 6))
  - Outgoing Correspondence –1962 –1964—D –G (Box 91, Folder 7))
  - Outgoing Correspondence—1962 –1963—H—J (Box 91, Folder 8))
  - Outgoing Correspondence—1963 –1964—K – Ma (Box 91, Folder 9))
  - Outgoing Correspondence—1960- 1964—Mc – Mu (Box 91, Folder 10))
  - Outgoing Correspondence—1963-1964—Ne – Sister (Box 91, Folder 11))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Abbott – Allen (Box 92, Folder 1))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Armand, Donald (Box 92, Folder 2))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Arrowsmith, Barbara (Box 92, Folder 3))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Bair, Clifford – Bryant, Marshall (Box 92, Folder 4))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Bube, Donald – Carley, James (Box 92, Folder 5))
  - Incoming from NATS Officials—Carter, Joel (Box 92, Folder 6))
  - Incoming from NATS Officials—Chamlee, Ruth Miller (1) (Box 92, Folder 7))
  - Incoming from NATS Officials –Chamlee, Ruth Miller (2) (Box 92, Folder 8))
  - Incoming from NATS Officials –Clark, Diane (Box 92, Folder 9))
  - Incoming from NATS Officials—Clark, Dr. Diane M. (Box 92, Folder 10))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Collins, Irma Helen (Box 92, Folder 11))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Cowden, Dr. R. H. (Box 92, Folder 12))
  - Incoming from NATS Officials—Cox, George (1) (Box 92, Folder 13))
  - Incoming from NATS Officials –Cox, George (2) (Box 92, Folder 14))
  - Incoming from NATS Officials –Crawford, Hadley R. (Box 92, Folder 15))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Crawford, Winfield (Box 92, Folder 16))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Cruser, Helen S. – Douglas, Mrs. Vivian C. (Box 92, Folder 17))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Downing, Dr. Bob (Box 92, Folder 18))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Ducrest, Willis –Dunkley, Ferdinand (Box 93, Folder 1))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Eberl, William – Elsey, Ellis (Box 93, Folder 2))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Elson, June – Emmons,Shirlee (Box 93, Folder 3))
  - Incoming from NATS Official –Engelstad, Paul (Box 93, Folder 4))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Enrico, Margaret Souders – Evans, Margaret (Box 93, Folder 5))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence –Ferrell, Ernestine – Fields, Victor A. (Box 93, Folder 6))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Fossey, Mrs. Elisabeth Jarrell (1) (Box 93, Folder 7))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Fossey, Mrs. Elisabeth Jarrell (2) (Box 93, Folder 8))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence –Garlinghouse, Burton (Box 93, Folder 9))
  - Incoming Member Correpondence—Gephart, William – Griffith, Katherine E. (Box 93, Folder 10))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Grimm, Betty Jane – Halliday, Dr. John R. (Box 93, Folder 11))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Halling, Elias J. – Hanke, Arline (Johnson) (Box 93, Folder 12))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence – Hanvey, A.E. – Hoffelt, Robert O. (Box 93, Folder 13))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Hoffpauir, Mrs. H.L. – Hovey (Box 93, Folder 14))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Hugoboom, R. Wayne – Johnson, Donald Egbert (Box 94, Folder 1))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Johnson, Violet – Johnson, Zoe Musgrave (Box 94, Folder 2))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Jones, Philip – Kelton, Mrs. Allen (Box 94, Folder 3))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Kinsinger, Dan H. (Box 94, Folder 4))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Kockritz – Kommel, Margret (Box 94, Folder 5))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Kremer, Jeannette (Box 94, Folder 6))
  - Lncoming Member Correspondence—Kroepfl, M. – Light, John (Box 94, Folder 7))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence – Linney, Virginia (Box 94, Folder 8))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Long, Berte – Lyon, Helen (Box 94, Folder 9))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence –Mabry, Sharon—McBurney (Box 94, Folder 10))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence –McClung, Martha Dick (Box 94, Folder 11))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—McCook, Lillian G. – McKissack (Box 94, Folder 12))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence –Mack, Gladys –Massie, Mary Fitzsimmons (Box 94, Folder 13))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Mauch, Diane F. (Box 94, Folder 14))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence – Mendenhall –Metzger (Box 95, Folder 1))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence –Miller, Katherine Shaw –Murphy, Lloyd (Box 95, Folder 2))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Murray, Catharine –Ohl, Dr. Ferris E. (Box 95, Folder 3))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Orpen, Ethel W. –Parker, Ruth (Box 95, Folder 4))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Partridge, Robert – Peterson, Paul (Box 95, Folder 5))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—NATS – Phillips (Box 95, Folder 6))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence ---Pierce, Charles L. –Ragatz, Ruth Hammond (Box 95, Folder 7))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Recital 1976 – Rogers, Carl (Box 95, Folder 8))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Ross, William—Schirmer, Allan (Box 95, Folder 9))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence---Schneider, Edythe – Seitz, Harry (Box 95, Folder 10))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Shaffer, Jeanne – Skitch, Russell (Box 95, Folder 11))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Skurdalsvold, Jennie – Snyder, Mrs. J. N. (Box 95, Folder 12))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Sollenberger, Arlene – Sutherlin, Mrs. L.L. (Box 95, Folder 13))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Swanson, Frederick – Tellinghuisen (Box 96, Folder 1))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Thomas, Zelma Lee –Titcomb, Louise C. (Box 96, Folder 2))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence –Toms, John –White, Quillian (Box 96, Folder 3))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Whitlock, Weldon –Wolanski, Helen (Box 96, Folder 4))
  - Incoming NATS Official—Wolfman, Mary (Box 96, Folder 5))
  - Incoming Member Correspondence—Wright, Neil –Ziegler, Dorothy (Box 96, Folder 6))
  - Incoming NATS –1962 (Box 96, Folder 7))
  - Incoming NATS—1963 (Box 96, Folder 8))
  - Incoming NATS—Possible Convention Locations, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 9))
  - Incoming NATS—Possible Convention Locations, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 10))
  - Incoming NATS—Committee on Vocal Affairs in the Public Schools (Box 96, Folder 11))
  - Incoming NATS—Former Members’ Resignations (Box 96, Folder 12))
  - Incoming NATS, 1990-1999 (Box 96, Folder 13))
  - NATS—Memoranda re: Reinstatements, 1962 –1964 (Box 97, Folder 1))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, 1960 – 1962 (Box 97, Folder 2))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 3))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, 1962 (Box 97, Folder 4))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, January 1962 – December 1963 (Box 97, Folder 5))
  - NATS—Louis Nicholas, President—Correspondence—1963 and Convention Programs, 1962, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 6))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, January – March 1963 (Box 97, Folder 7))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, April – July 1963 (Box 97, Folder 8))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, July – August 1963 (Box 97, Folder 9))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, September 1963 (Box 97, Folder 10))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, October – November 1963 (Box 97, Folder 11))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, Nov. – December 1963 (Box 97, Folder 12))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, January 1964 (Box 97, Folder 13))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, January – November 1964 (Box 97, Folder 14))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, January – December 1964 (Box 97, Folder 15))
  - NATS—Correspondence, Memoranda, January 1965 – January 1966 (Box 97, Folder 16))
  - NATS—Address Bulletins, 1962 –1963 (Box 98, Folder 1))
  - NATS—Policy Board, Official Communications, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 2))
  - NATS—Executive Board, Official Correspondence, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 3))
  - NATS—Executive Board, Official Correspondence, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 4))
  - NATS—Policy Board, Official Communications, 1963 –1964 (Box 98, Folder 5))
  - NATS—Executive Board, Official Correspondence, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 6))
  - NATS—Board Minutes, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 7))
  - NATS—Board Minutes and Board Letters, (1984 – July 1985) (Box 98, Folder 8))
  - NATS—Board Minutes, December 26, 1996 – Dec. 30, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 9))
  - NATS—Board Letter No. I, 15 February 1997 (Box 98, Folder 10))
  - NATS—Executive Board Meeting Minutes August 2, 1997; Financial Statement, Dec. 1976 (Box 98, Folder 11))
  - NATS—Memoranda August 19, 2002—Financial Report (Box 98, Folder 12))
  - NATS—Records, Membership Lists, 1944 – 1956 (Box 99, Folder 1))
  - NATS—Membership List, August 1946 (Box 99, Folder 2))
  - NATS—Membership Lists, 1952, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 3))
  - NATS—Membership List, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 4))
  - NATS—Membership Lists, 1962, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 5))
  - NATS—Membership Directory, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 6))
  - NATS—Nashville Chapter Membership, 1974 and other materials (Box 99, Folder 7))
  - NATS—Nashville Membership, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 8))
  - NATS—Membership Directory, 1983 (Box 99, Folder 9))
  - 1983 and other lists (Box 99, Folder 10) NATS—Membership List (Nashville Area))
  - NATS—Membership Invitations, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 11))
  - NATS—Membership Directory, July 1992 (Box 99, Folder 12))
  - NATS—Membership, Board Meetings, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 13))
  - NATS—Membership Directory, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 14))
  - NATS—Membership, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 1))
  - NATS—Membership 1995, Officers and Board (Box 100, Folder 2))
  - NATS—Membership, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 3))
  - NATS—Membership Directory, July 1998 (Box 100, Folder 4))
  - NATS—Members List 11-16-98 in Zip Code order (Box 100, Folder 5))
  - NATS—Membership, Elections, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 6))
  - NATS—Membership, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 7))
  - NATS—Membership Directory, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 8))
  - NATS—Election to Membership Lists and Member Changes, 2000-2001 (Box 100, Folder 9))
  - NATS—Membership Directory, April 2002 (Box 100, Folder 10))
  - NATS—Membership Lists (Box 100, Folder 11))
  - NATS—Members in Tennessee, Alabama, Kentucky; Proposed statement of organization and procedure (Box 100, Folder 12))
  - NATS—Convention in Chicago 1951—Travel request to Peabody College (Box 101, Folder 1))
  - NATS—Members at Conventions, 1954, 1957 (Box 101, Folder 2))
  - NATS—Convention Programs, 1954, 1955, 1958, 1959, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 3))
  - NATS—Convention Programs, 1962, 1963, 1964, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 4))
  - NATS—Convention Programs, 1966, 1967, 1971, 1972, 1973,1974 (Box 101, Folder 5))
  - NATS—New York Convention, 1959 (Box 101, Folder 6))
  - NATS—Registration Lists, (1961, 1962, 1965, 1969, 1970, 1971) (Box 101, Folder 7))
  - NATS—Membership list, Convention Registration(1965, 1966); By-laws 1966-Revised (Box 101, Folder 8))
  - NATS—Prospectus for convention at Los Angeles Biltmore (Box 101, Folder 9))
  - NATS—Silver Jubilee Convention, Dec. 1969 (Box 101, Folder 10))
  - NATS—Silver Jubilee Convention “Songs You May Not Know” by L.N. 1969, 1970 Convention Program; other NATS Programs (Box 101, Folder 11))
  - NATS—Registration List—29th Annual Convention—New York City (Box 101, Folder 12))
  - NATS—Program and Registration List—30th Anniversary Convention, Indianapolis, Dec. 27-30, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 13))
  - NATS –Convention Program (31st) December 1976, Philadelphia, PA (Box 101, Folder 14))
  - NATS—Programs from July 1983 Convention in Minneapolis, Minnesota (Box 101, Folder 15))
  - NATS—Programs from December 1984 Convention in New Orleans, Louisiana (Box 101, Folder 16))
  - NATS—Programs from July 1986 National Convention in Chicago, Illinois (Box 101, Folder 17))
  - NATS—July 1986 Convention in Chicago, Illinois—Maps, Theatre Guide, etc. (Box 101, Folder 18))
  - NATS—Program of 37th National Convention, Chicago, Illinois, July 17-21, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 19))
  - NATS—Chicago Convention, July 1986 (Box 101, Folder 20))
  - NATS—Materials for National Convention July 1 –5, 1992 (Boston Park Plaza Hotel and Towers) (Box 101, Folder 21))
  - NATS—1987, 1992, 1993 Convention Lists and Information (Box 101, Folder 22))
  - NATS—45th Convention, 1998—Toronto, Canada (Box 101, Folder 23))
  - NATS—Program for the 46th National Convention, Philadelphia, Master Class with Paul Plishka, July 1, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 24))
  - NATS—2000 Convention—Bylaws (Box 101, Folder 25))
  - NATS—Program—Recital July 3, 2000-46th National Convention (Box 101, Folder 26))
  - NATS—Workshop, August 1954 (Box 102, Folder 1))
  - NATS—List of Contemporary American Songs for Teaching and Recital Use with accompanying article for NATS workshops, August 1954 (Box 102, Folder 2))
  - NATS—Summer Workshops 1955, 1956; other materials (Box 102, Folder 3))
  - NATS –Workshops, 1956, 1957 (Box 102, Folder 4))
  - NATS—Notebook and Program—Emory University, August 19 –23, 1957 (Box 102, Folder 5))
  - NATS—Workshop “The Vocal Foundation” (Box 102, Folder 6))
  - NATS—Publicity Releases, etc. 1958, Louis Nicholas, Vice-President (Box 102, Folder 7))
  - NATS—Kansas City Area Chapter (1961-62, 1962-63, 1963-64); Los Angeles Chapter (Box 102, Folder 8))
  - NATS—Workshop 1962, Kansas City, Missouri (Box 102, Folder 9))
  - NATS—University of Colorado NATS Workshop, July 19-24th, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 10))
  - NATS—University of Colorado NATS Workshop July 19-24, 1964 (including “The Teaching of William Vilonat” by Vera B. McIntyre) (Box 102, Folder 11))
  - NATS—University of Colorado NATS Workshop—Lists of Songs Prepared by L.N., July 1964 (Box 102, Folder 12))